Fred Crawford Papers
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 6. Lowell Thomas Papers Research File, 6; Boxes: 52 - 169
  - Princeton Grad Alumni, 1944 - 1980 (Folder 4, Box 134)
  - Prison B - C Flap, 1935 (Folder 5, Box 134)
  - Prisoner, 1938 (Folder 6, Box 134)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] " Pro - German " APR, 1942 April (Folder 7, Box 134)
  - Proctor & Gamble, 1946 - 1953 (Folder 8, Box 134)
  - Pronunciation, 1932 - 1962 (Folder 9, Box 134)
  - Pronunciation Appreciation, 1940 - 1945 (Folder 10, Box 134)
  - Proudly We Hail, 1941 (Folder 11, Box 134)
  - Publicity Stunts, undated (Folder 12, Box 134)
  - Publishers, 1940 - 1976 (Folder 13, Box 134)
  - Pultzer (Collings), 1940 (Folder 14, Box 134)
  - Pyle, 1945? - 1959 (Folder 15, Box 134)
  - Pryors, 1938 - 1980 (Folder 16, Box 134)
  - Quaker Hill, 1932 - 1980 (Folder 17, Box 134)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Book, 1939 - 1980 (Folder 18, Box 134)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Branch, 1936 - 1943 (Folder 19, Box 134)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] burial Ground Assignment Branch, 1945 - 1981 (Folder 20, Box 134)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] - Carpenter, 1944 - 1946 (Folder 1, Box 135)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Carson Flap, 1953 (Folder 2, Box 135)
  - Quaker Hill Civic Organization, 1980 (Folder 3, Box 135)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Coffin, 1978 (Folder 4, Box 135)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Cook, Tela, 1966 - 1979 (Folder 5, Box 135)
  - QHCC [Quaker Hill Country Club] [1 of 3], 1937 - 1941 (Folder 6, Box 135)
  - QHCC [Quaker Hill Country Club] [2 of 3], 1941 - 1961 (Folder 7, Box 135)
  - QHCC [Quaker Hill Country Club] [3 of 3], 1961 - 1981 (Folder 8, Box 135)
  - QHCC [Quaker Hill Country Club] Barn, 1961? (Folder 9, Box 135)
  - QHCC [Quaker Hill Country Club] Durlacher, Ed, 1941 - 1946 (Folder 10, Box 135)
  - QHCC [Quaker Hill Country Club] Growing, 1945 - 1949 (Folder 11, Box 135)
  - QHCC [Quaker Hill Country Club] - Jones, 1939 - 1940 (Folder 12, Box 135)
  - QHCC [Quaker Hill Country Club] Club House, 1941 (Folder 13, Box 135)
  - QHCC [Quaker Hill Country Club] Opening, 1941 (Folder 14, Box 135)
  - QHCC [Quaker Hill Country Club] - Shaw, 1941 - 1975 (Folder 15, Box 135)
  - QHCC [Quaker Hill Country Club] - Wollsteiner, undated (Folder 16, Box 135)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Dewey, 1947 (Folder 17, Box 135)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Employees, 1941 (Folder 18, Box 135)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Farm Owner's List, 1926? (Folder 19, Box 135)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Fine, 1940 (Folder 20, Box 135)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] French, 1931 - 1981 (Folder 21, Box 135)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Glider, 1942 (Folder 22, Box 135)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Harkness, 1950 - 1953 (Folder 23, Box 135)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Inn, 1942 - 1947 (Folder 24, Box 135)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Keefe, Charles S., 1941 - 1952 (Folder 25, Box 135)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Knoll Cottage, 1945 - 1975 (Folder 26, Box 135)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Kosmak, 1953 (Folder 27, Box 135)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Mason, 1941 (Folder 28, Box 135)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Museum, 1953 - 1970 (Folder 29, Box 135)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] O'Hara, 1967 (Folder 30, Box 135)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Orton, 1975 (Folder 31, Box 135)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Parcels (1) [1 of 2], 1932 - 1938 (Folder 1, Box 136)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Parcels (1) [2 of 2], 1938 - 1982 (Folder 2, Box 136)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Parcels (2) [1 of 3], 1932 - 1941 (Folder 3, Box 136)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Parcels (2) [2 of 3], 1941 - 1952 (Folder 4, Box 136)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Parcels (2) [3 of 3], 1952 - 1982 (Folder 5, Box 136)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Parcels ?, 1934 (Folder 6, Box 136)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Parcels - Hammersley Hill, 1972 (Folder 7, Box 136)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Parker, Dan, 1941 - 1946 (Folder 8, Box 136)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Peale, 1942 (Folder 9, Box 136)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Pearson Flap, undated (Folder 10, Box 136)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Plans (Branch Letter), 1941 (Folder 11, Box 136)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Questionnaire, 1939 (Folder 12, Box 136)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Recruit, 1937 - 1938 (Folder 13, Box 136)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] - Reader, 1940 - 1941 (Folder 14, Box 136)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Reinhold, Ralph, 1938 - 1946 (Folder 15, Box 136)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Restrictions, 1938 - 1976 (Folder 1, Box 137)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Roads, 1934 - 1972 (Folder 2, Box 137)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Rod & Gun Club, 1941 (Folder 3, Box 137)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Security, 1940 - 1981 (Folder 4, Box 137)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Sheep, 1933 - 1938 (Folder 5, Box 137)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Sibley, 1942 - 1973 (Folder 6, Box 137)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Ski, 1939 - 1971 (Folder 7, Box 137)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Ski Lists, 1942 - 1952 (Folder 8, Box 137)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Steele, Majorie, 1940 (Folder 9, Box 137)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Steeple, 1940 - 1960 (Folder 10, Box 137)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Strawberry Hill, 1939 - 1970 (Folder 11, Box 137)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Sun, 1938 - 1942 (Folder 12, Box 137)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Syndicate, 1938 (Folder 13, Box 137)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Trees, 1939 (Folder 14, Box 137)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Warrick, 1939 (Folder 15, Box 137)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Warwick Flap, undated (Folder 16, Box 137)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Williams, 1940 (Folder 17, Box 137)
  - QH [Quaker Hill] Zoning, 1973 (Folder 18, Box 137)
  - Q [Quaker] Lake, 1934 - 1981 (Folder 19, Box 137)
  - Q [Quaker] Lake Observatory, 1934 - 1944 (Folder 20, Box 137)
  - Quaker Lake Rights, 1939 - 1976 (Folder 21, Box 137)
  - Queen Elizabeth, 1976 (Folder 22, Box 137)
  - Quinby Plan, 1941 - 1948 (Folder 23, Box 137)
  - Quisling, 1941 (Folder 24, Box 137)
  - Racial, 1934 - 1952 (Folder 25, Box 137)
  - Radio, 1941 - 1978 (Folder 26, Box 137)
  - Radio Autograph, 1932 - 1935 (Folder 27, Box 137)
  - Radio Career, 1930 (Folder 1, Box 138)
  - Radio City, 1934 (Folder 2, Box 138)
  - Radio Correspondents, 1951 (Folder 3, Box 138)
  - Radio Debut (News), 1930 September 30 (Folder 4, Box 138)
  - Radio Flap, 1937 - 1960 (Folder 5, Box 138)
  - Radio Free Asia, 1967 - 1969 (Folder 6, Box 138)
  - Radio History, 1940 - 1967 (Folder 7, Box 138)
  - Radio Ideas, 1932 - 1951 (Folder 8, Box 138)
  - Radio Insurance, 1943 (Folder 9, Box 138)
  - Radio - Milne Flap, 1943 (Folder 10, Box 138)
  - Radio Pioneers, 1947 - 1955 (Folder 11, Box 138)
  - Radio Staff, 1931 - 1960 (Folder 12, Box 138)
  - Radio vs TV Listings, 1966 (Folder 13, Box 138)
  - Rafferty, 1964 - 1967 (Folder 14, Box 138)
  - Raiders, 1929 - 1963 (Folder 15, Box 138)
  - Ranch, 1913 - 1952 (Folder 16, Box 138)
  - Rand, Ayn, 1940 (Folder 17, Box 138)
  - Rankin (Mother), 1940 - 1958 (Folder 18, Box 138)
  - RAO on LT [Lowell Thomas], 1966 - 1970 (Folder 19, Box 138)
  - Rappaport, 1948 (Folder 20, Box 138)
  - Ratings, 1931 - 1976 (Folder 21, Box 138)
  - RD [Readers Digest], 1934 - 1981 (Folder 22, Box 138)
  - RD [Readers Digest] Alaska, 1959 (Folder 23, Box 138)
  - RD [Readers Digest] Foundation, 1948 - 1975 (Folder 24, Box 138)
  - RD [Readers Digest] - Murrow, 1968 - 1969 (Folder 25, Box 138)
  - Reagan, 1973 - 1981 (Folder 26, Box 138)
  - Redants, Parastory, 1945 (Folder 27, Box 138)
  - Redwoods (QH [Quaker Hill?]), 1950 - 1962 (Folder 28, Box 138)
  - Reed, Joseph Vernon, Jr., 1962 - 1981 (Folder 29, Box 138)
  - Reedy, Admiral J.R., 1964 - 1974 (Folder 30, Box 138)
  - Reeve, Bob, 1937 - 1968 (Folder 31, Box 138)
  - References by LT [Lowell Thomas], 1936 - 1964 (Folder 1, Box 139)
  - Reid, James (Ghost?), 1969 - 1972 (Folder 2, Box 139)
  - Remote, 1930 - 1966 (Folder 3, Box 139)
  - Remote B - C Ethics (Sharon), 1934 (Folder 4, Box 139)
  - " Repairs " B - C, 1932 - 1970 (Folder 5, Box 139)
  - Req, 1930s (Folder 6, Box 139)
  - Requests, 1940s (Folder 7, Box 139)
  - Req, 1950s (Folder 8, Box 139)
  - Req, 1960s (Folder 9, Box 139)
  - Requests, 1970 (Folder 1, Box 140)
  - " Requests ", 1939 - 1951 (Folder 2, Box 140)
  - Request - Action, 1959 - 1981 (Folder 3, Box 140)
  - Requests - Autograph, 1939 - 1960 (Folder 4, Box 140)
  - Request Blurbs, 1978 - 1981 (Folder 5, Box 140)
  - Book/MS Requests, 1938 - 1952 (Folder 6, Box 140)
  - Request - Botch, 1941 (Folder 7, Box 140)
  - Requests - Endorse, 1935 - 1981 (Folder 8, Box 140)
  - Request Flap - McCloskey, 1939 (Folder 9, Box 140)
  - Requests - Information, 1933 - 1981 (Folder 10, Box 140)
  - Requests - Interview, 1934 - 1981 (Folder 11, Box 140)
  - Requests - Job, 1934 - 1958 (Folder 12, Box 140)
  - Request - Loan, 1961 - 1980 (Folder 13, Box 140)
  - Request - Money, 1933 - 1981 (Folder 14, Box 140)
  - Requests - Multiple, 1938 (Folder 15, Box 140)
  - Requests - No, undated (Folder 16, Box 140)
  - Requests - Permissions, 1946 - 1981 (Folder 17, Box 140)
  - Requests - Prints, 1981 (Folder 18, Box 140)
  - Requests - Stough, 1961 (Folder 19, Box 140)
  - Requests - String Pull, 1933 - 1981 (Folder 20, Box 140)
  - Requests - " Touches ", 1934 - 1952 (Folder 21, Box 140)
  - RESIG (Club), 1940 - 1980 (Folder 22, Box 140)
  - " Retirement ", April 1976 (Folder 23, Box 140)
  - Reusswig & Sawyers, 1961 (Folder 24, Box 140)
  - Reuell, Nellie, 1934 - 1980 (Folder 25, Box 140)
  - Reynolds, Quentin, 1941 - 1950 (Folder 26, Box 140)
  - Rhino (April 1971), 1967 - 1977 (Folder 27, Box 140)
  - Richards, Bob, 1960 (Folder 28, Box 140)
  - Richards, Herb, 1965 - 1977 (Folder 1, Box 141)
  - Richmond, Indiana, undated (Folder 2, Box 141)
  - Richter, undated (Folder 3, Box 141)
  - Rickenbecker, 1935 - 1978 (Folder 4, Box 141)
  - Richardson, Hugh, 1953 - 1954 (Folder 5, Box 141)
  - Richardson, Hugh, 1953 - 1980 (Folder 6, Box 141)
  - Rickey, Branch, 1946 (Folder 7, Box 141)
  - NYT Magazine Riley Article, 1915 September 12 (Folder 8, Box 141)
  - Ringling, 1932 - 1967 (Folder 9, Box 141)
  - Ripley, 1938 (Folder 10, Box 141)
  - Rittenhouse, Paul (NBC), 1977 (Folder 11, Box 141)
  - Rizzuto, Phil, 1961 - 1975 (Folder 12, Box 141)
  - Roberson, 1953 - 1982 (Folder 13, Box 141)
  - Roberts, John, 1942 - 1975 (Folder 14, Box 141)
  - Roberts, Oral, 1975 - 1980 (Folder 15, Box 141)
  - Robinson, Joseph, 1941 - 1958 (Folder 16, Box 141)
  - Robinson, Lee, 1959 - 1981 (Folder 17, Box 141)
  - Rockefeller L - R, undated (Folder 18, Box 141)
  - Rochford, Daniel, 1975 (Folder 19, Box 141)
  - Rockefeller, Laurence S., 1958 - 1966 (Folder 20, Box 141)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson, 1960 - 1970 (Folder 21, Box 141)
  - Rockefeller, Winthrop, 1939 - 1973 (Folder 22, Box 141)
  - Rockefeller CTR Magazine, 1939 - 1940 (Folder 23, Box 141)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1942 (Folder 24, Box 141)
  - Rodgers, Richard, 1955 (Folder 25, Box 141)
  - Roelofs, 1951 - 1971 (Folder 26, Box 141)
  - Rodgers, Will, 1935 - 1980 (Folder 27, Box 141)
  - Rolling Stone, 1931 - 1955 (Folder 28, Box 141)
  - Romulo (GHCC), 1956 (Folder 29, Box 141)
  - Ronne, Finn, 1940 - 1979 (Folder 30, Box 141)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1933 - 1962 (Folder 31, Box 141)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1932 - 1982 (Folder 1, Box 142)
  - Roosevelt, Leila, 1934 - 1966 (Folder 2, Box 142)
  - Roosevelt, Quentin, 1946 - 1948 (Folder 3, Box 142)
  - FDR [Franklin D. Roosevelt] Banquet, 1939 (Folder 4, Box 142)
  - Roosevelt Dog B - C, 1945 (Folder 5, Box 142)
  - Roosevelts (Oysteruelets), 1935 - 1944 (Folder 6, Box 142)
  - Ross, Lenny, 1977 (Folder 7, Box 142)
  - Ross, Father William, 1973 (Folder 8, Box 142)
  - Rossi, Jean Thomas, 1941 - 1979 (Folder 9, Box 142)
  - Rotary, 1980 (Folder 10, Box 142)
  - Rower Boys, 1944 - 1947 (Folder 11, Box 142)
  - Royal Geo Soc., 1932 - 1952 (Folder 12, Box 142)
  - Ruddeel, 1953 (Folder 13, Box 142)
  - Rusk, Howard A., 1944 - 1980 (Folder 14, Box 142)
  - Russia, 1958 - 1959 (Folder 15, Box 142)
  - Russian Relief, 1943 - 1944 (Folder 16, Box 142)
  - Russo, MSGR Dominic, 1981 (Folder 17, Box 142)
  - Ruth, Babe, 1935 (Folder 18, Box 142)
  - Ryan, F. Lamb, 1911 - 1974 (Folder 19, Box 142)
  - Ryan, Mrs. H. P. (1869 - 1948), 1947 - 1949 (Folder 20, Box 142)
  - Ryan, Joe, 1981 (Folder 21, Box 142)
  - Ryan, Norm (Jr.), 1938 (Folder 22, Box 142)
  - Ryan, Norm A., 1944 - 1947 (Folder 23, Box 142)
  - Ryan, Royal, 1932 - 1957 (Folder 24, Box 142)
  - Ryan, T. S., 1922 (Folder 25, Box 142)
  - Ryans, 1935 - 1980 (Folder 26, Box 142)
  - Sabin, Thomas S., 1962 (Folder 27, Box 142)
  - Sacketts, 1940 (Folder 28, Box 142)
  - Safari, 1965 (Folder 29, Box 142)
  - " Safe " Advocate (Geo Merrill), 1940 (Folder 30, Box 142)
  - " Safety ", 1955 - 1956 (Folder 31, Box 142)
  - SAGA, 1934 - 1946 (Folder 32, Box 142)
  - Said, Nuri, 1945 (Folder 33, Box 142)
  - St. Lawrence Seaway/ N.Y. Throughway, 1962 (Folder 34, Box 142)
  - St. Peter, Ann, 1940 - 1975 (Folder 35, Box 142)
  - Saints & Sinners, 1939 - 1957 (Folder 36, Box 142)
  - Salant, 1979 - 1980 (Folder 37, Box 142)
  - Salary (1952?), 1935 - 1978 (Folder 38, Box 142)
  - Salisbury, H.H., 1942 - 1980 (Folder 39, Box 142)
  - Salzburg (land), 1964 (Folder 40, Box 142)
  - Sanger, 1935 (Folder 41, Box 142)
  - Sanita Hills, 1941 - 1944 (Folder 1, Box 143)
  - Santa Claus, 1950 (Folder 2, Box 143)
  - Sarazen, Gene, 1940 - 1980 (Folder 3, Box 143)
  - Samoff, 1944 - 1971 (Folder 4, Box 143)
  - Satellites, 1946 (Folder 5, Box 143)
  - Saturday Evening Post, 1973 - 1976 (Folder 6, Box 143)
  - Sauage, Raymond, 1948 (Folder 7, Box 143)
  - Sawyer, John P., 1943 - 1978 (Folder 8, Box 143)
  - Sawyer, Johnny, 1958 - 1968 (Folder 9, Box 143)
  - Scam, 1940 (Folder 10, Box 143)
  - Scam (Fiaschetti Dinner), 1934 (Folder 11, Box 143)
  - Schaeffler, 1955 (Folder 12, Box 143)
  - Schechter, Abe, 1940 - 1980 (Folder 13, Box 143)
  - Schemes, 1938 (Folder 14, Box 143)
  - Schlegel, Paul, 1931 (Folder 15, Box 143)
  - Schoonmaker, Frank, 1930 - 1943 (Folder 16, Box 143)
  - Schumann - Heink, 1922? (Folder 17, Box 143)
  - Schuster, Max, 1971 (Folder 18, Box 143)
  - Schwamb, 1943 - 1953 (Folder 19, Box 143)
  - Schwarzkupf, 1939 (Folder 20, Box 143)
  - Scott, Adelaide, 1955 - 1972 (Folder 21, Box 143)
  - Scott, Henry L, 1950 (Folder 22, Box 143)
  - Scott, Jack, 1963 - 1966 (Folder 23, Box 143)
  - Scott, Sheila, undated (Folder 24, Box 143)
  - Scripts (Misc.), 1932 - 1950 (Folder 25, Box 143)
  - Sea Devil, 1928 (Folder 26, Box 143)
  - Sea Devil Script, 1927? (Folder 27, Box 143)
  - See, Henry (BBD & O), 1966 - 1978 (Folder 28, Box 143)
  - " See Am " Campaign, 1915 - 1917 (Folder 29, Box 143)
  - Seeger, Peter (Matt), 1967 (Folder 30, Box 143)
  - " Seeing ", 1933 - 1951 (Folder 31, Box 143)
  - Seiler (Garsy), 1944 - 1975 (Folder 32, Box 143)
  - Seldes, 1948 (Folder 33, Box 143)
  - Selig, 1937 - 1969 (Folder 34, Box 143)
  - Senykoff, Ron, 1969 - 1981 (Folder 35, Box 143)
  - Seppala, 1961 - 1968 (Folder 36, Box 143)
  - Seraphics, 1946 - 1975 (Folder 37, Box 143)
  - Seuareid, 1947 - 1974 (Folder 38, Box 143)
  - Shah of Iran, undated (Folder 39, Box 143)
  - Shalley, 1932 - 1955 (Folder 40, Box 143)
  - Shane, Ted, 1938 - 1967 (Folder 41, Box 143)
  - Sherwin, Louis, 1937 - 1978 (Folder 42, Box 143)
  - Sherwood, Bob, 1931 - 1935 (Folder 43, Box 143)
  - Sheilds, Don, 1953 - 1957 (Folder 44, Box 143)
  - Shirer, Bill, 1943 (Folder 45, Box 143)
  - Short Wave, 1931 - 1950 (Folder 1, Box 144)
  - June 1970 Serbia, 1970 - 1974 (Folder 2, Box 144)
  - Serbia Scripts, 1970 (Folder 3, Box 144)
  - 1912 Sigma Delta Chi, 1966 - 1968 (Folder 4, Box 144)
  - Sills, Beverly, 1974 (Folder 5, Box 144)
  - Silurians, 1981 (Folder 6, Box 144)
  - Silver (Hi Ho), 1965 (Folder 7, Box 144)
  - Simon Fraser Winv., 1967 - 1981 (Folder 8, Box 144)
  - Simplot, 1962 - 1980 (Folder 9, Box 144)
  - Simpson, Anita, 1938 - 1957 (Folder 10, Box 144)
  - Singapore to Mandalay Book, 1931 (Folder 11, Box 144)
  - Singing Lady, undated (Folder 12, Box 144)
  - Ski, 1933 - 1944 (Folder 13, Box 144)
  - Ski, 1944 - 1948 (Folder 14, Box 144)
  - Ski, 1949 - 1952 (Folder 15, Box 144)
  - Ski, 1953 - 1959 (Folder 16, Box 144)
  - Ski, 1960 - 1964 (Folder 17, Box 144)
  - Ski, 1965 - 1967 (Folder 1, Box 145)
  - Ski, 1963 (Folder 2, Box 145)
  - Ski, 1969 - 1972 (Folder 3, Box 145)
  - Ski, 1973 - 1976 (Folder 4, Box 145)
  - Ski, 1977 - 1994 (Folder 5, Box 145)
  - Ski, undated (Folder 6, Box 145)
  - Ski [Age], 1977 - 1981 (Folder 7, Box 145)
  - Ski - Allais, 1948 - 1949 (Folder 8, Box 145)
  - Ski - Alta, 1949 - 1969 (Folder 9, Box 145)
  - Ski - Ankle, 1953 (Folder 10, Box 145)
  - Ski - Apsen, 1946 - 1966 (Folder 11, Box 145)
  - Ski - Background, 1928 - 1981 (Folder 12, Box 145)
  - Ski (Bousquet), 1937 - 1981 (Folder 13, Box 145)
  - Ski - Bromley, 1955 (Folder 14, Box 145)
  - Ski (Catamount), 1969 - 1973 (Folder 15, Box 145)
  - Ski Citations (Mock), undated (Folder 16, Box 145)
  - Ski - Contests, 1946 - 1948 (Folder 17, Box 145)
  - Ski - Film, 1941 - 1942 (Folder 18, Box 145)
  - Ski - Gow, 1975 (Folder 19, Box 145)
  - 1966 June Ski Hall of Fame, 1966 - 1978 (Folder 20, Box 145)
  - Ski History, 1977 - 1981 (Folder 21, Box 145)
  - Ski Industry $ fm LT [Lowell Thomas], 1940 (Folder 22, Box 145)
  - Ski Lake Placid, 1933 - 1973 (Folder 23, Box 145)
  - Ski - Law, 1941 - 1948 (Folder 24, Box 145)
  - Ski - Mad River (Palmedo), 1947 - 1958 (Folder 1, Box 146)
  - Ski - Madonna, 1966 - 1973 (Folder 2, Box 146)
  - Ski - Mammoth Mountain, undated (Folder 3, Box 146)
  - Ski - Mont Tremblant, 1938 - 1974 (Folder 4, Box 146)
  - Ski - Mt Juneau, 1973 (Folder 5, Box 146)
  - Ski (Mt Mansfield, Rusch, Chimo, Stowe), 1942 - 1975 (Folder 6, Box 146)
  - Ski - Mt Washington, 1979 (Folder 7, Box 146)
  - Ski - Museum, 1965 (Folder 8, Box 146)
  - National Ski Patrol, 1939 - 1976 (Folder 9, Box 146)
  - Ski - National Ski Week, 1948 (Folder 10, Box 146)
  - Ski - Pfeiffer, 1961 - 1962 (Folder 11, Box 146)
  - Ski - Sahuaro Ski Club, 1944 - 1958 (Folder 12, Box 146)
  - Ski " Scholar ", 1962 (Folder 13, Box 146)
  - Ski - Shane, 1940 - 1941 (Folder 14, Box 146)
  - Shane Ski Article, 1946 February 9 (Folder 15, Box 146)
  - Ski - Shurtees, 1961 - 1973 (Folder 16, Box 146)
  - Ski - Ski Bob, 1968 - 1970 (Folder 17, Box 146)
  - Ski Doo, 1969 (Folder 18, Box 146)
  - Ski - Stowe, 1938 - 1978 (Folder 19, Box 146)
  - Ski - Storm & Ryan, 1940 (Folder 20, Box 146)
  - Ski - Sun Valley, 1942 - 1976 (Folder 21, Box 146)
  - Ski - Tow Flap, 1946 (Folder 22, Box 146)
  - Ski Trophy, 1941 - 1948 (Folder 23, Box 146)
  - Ski - Vail, 1960 (Folder 24, Box 146)
  - Ski - Vend, 1961 - 1962 (Folder 25, Box 146)
  - Ski - Whiteface, 1944 - 1976 (Folder 26, Box 146)
  - Ski - World War II, 1942 (Folder 27, Box 146)
  - Skid, 1931 (Folder 28, Box 146)
  - Skouras, Spyros, 1940 - 1971 (Folder 29, Box 146)
  - Sluhan [Air Force One], 1960 - 1982 (Folder 30, Box 146)
  - Small, Ed, 1952 (Folder 31, Box 146)
  - Smith, Al, 1929 (1941) (Folder 32, Box 146)
  - Smith, C. Lawrence, 1947 (Folder 33, Box 146)
  - Smith, Frank, 1945 - 1966 (Folder 1, Box 147)
  - Smith, Frederic A., 1960 (Folder 2, Box 147)
  - Smith, Guy (Brekeley), 1939 (Folder 3, Box 147)
  - Smith, GLR, undated (Folder 4, Box 147)
  - Smith, H. Allen, 1962 - 1974 (Folder 5, Box 147)
  - Smith, Randy, 1966 - 1976 (Folder 6, Box 147)
  - Smith, Ross, 1921 (Folder 7, Box 147)
  - Smith - Johannsen (ski), 1968 - 1973 (Folder 8, Box 147)
  - Snow, Edgar, 1941 - 1978 (Folder 9, Box 147)
  - SNVB, 1936 (Folder 10, Box 147)
  - " So Long ", 1931 - 1943 (Folder 11, Box 147)
  - So Long Until Monday, 1935 (Folder 12, Box 147)
  - So Long Until Tomorrow, 1977 - 1980 (Folder 13, Box 147)
  - Social Security, 1936 (Folder 14, Box 147)
  - Softball, 1938 - 1940 (Folder 15, Box 147)
  - Softball, So What?, 1938 (Folder 16, Box 147)
  - Sairces, 1933 (Folder 17, Box 147)
  - South Am [America], 1943 (Folder 18, Box 147)
  - South America, 1951 (Folder 19, Box 147)
  - South American Broadcast, 1957? (Folder 20, Box 147)
  - Space, 1968 - 1979 (Folder 21, Box 147)
  - Spaw Book, 1932 (Folder 22, Box 147)
  - Spanish Civil War, 1938 (Folder 23, Box 147)
  - Speak, 1932 - 1978 (Folder 24, Box 147)
  - Speak - Advance Publicity, 1939 (Folder 25, Box 147)
  - Speak - IMPT, 1934 (Folder 26, Box 147)
  - Speaking Fees, 1937 - 1979 (Folder 1, Box 148)
  - Speech Notes, 1930 - 1980 (Folder 2, Box 148)
  - Spelling Bee, 1937 (Folder 3, Box 148)
  - Spellman, Francis, 1937 (Folder 4, Box 148)
  - Sponsors, 1930 - 1981 (Folder 5, Box 148)
  - Sponsors: St of Cal., 1943 - 1945 (Folder 6, Box 148)
  - Sports Illustrated, 1957 (Folder 7, Box 148)
  - Sprague, 1951 - 1978 (Folder 8, Box 148)
  - Springfield Plan, 1945 (Folder 9, Box 148)
  - Squalus, 1939 (Folder 10, Box 148)
  - Stallings, 1968 - 1971 (Folder 11, Box 148)
  - Stand Fast For Freedom, 1940 - 1962 (Folder 12, Box 148)
  - Stanton, Frank, 1966 - 1975 (Folder 13, Box 148)
  - Starlight, 1938 - 1981 (Folder 14, Box 148)
  - Stassen, Hatold, 1950 (Folder 15, Box 148)
  - Steeger, Henry " Harry ", 1971 (Folder 16, Box 148)
  - Steel, Lucy, 1964 (Folder 17, Box 148)
  - Steen, Charles (Wranium), 1969 (Folder 18, Box 148)
  - Sterling Institute, 1979 - 1981 (Folder 19, Box 148)
  - Stewart, Edna (Ice Man), 1944 - 1962 (Folder 20, Box 148)
  - Stewart, James K., 1930 (Folder 21, Box 148)
  - Stillwell, 1943 - 1944 (1975) (Folder 22, Box 148)
  - Stinchfield, 1950 - 1976 (Folder 23, Box 148)
  - Stoddart, Dick, 1940 (Folder 24, Box 148)
  - Stone, Donald L. " Gov ", 1947 - 1967 (Folder 25, Box 148)
  - Stone, Emerson, 1971 - 1972 (Folder 26, Box 148)
  - Stone, Fred/ Stone - Collins, Dorothy, 1952 - 1973 (Folder 27, Box 148)
  - Stoopnagle (F. Chase Taylor), 1938 - 1948 (Folder 28, Box 148)
  - Storrs, 1939 (Folder 1, Box 149)
  - Stout, Rex, 1943 - 1944 (Folder 2, Box 149)
  - Stowe Prep, 1960 - 1966 (Folder 3, Box 149)
  - Strange (Bowen) ( See Doubleday), 1967 - 1979 (Folder 4, Box 149)
  - Stranger Letters, 1967 - 1972 (Folder 5, Box 149)
  - Strauss, Lewis, 1954 - 1974 (Folder 6, Box 149)
  - Strawn, 1914 - 1976 (Folder 7, Box 149)
  - Strep, 1939 (Folder 8, Box 149)
  - Strike/Robt Graves, 1967 (Folder 9, Box 149)
  - Strom, 1937 - 1976 (Folder 10, Box 149)
  - Strong, Anne Louise, 1955 (Folder 11, Box 149)
  - Substitutes, 1934 - 1972 (Folder 12, Box 149)
  - Sullivan, Ed, 1958 (Folder 13, Box 149)
  - Summons, 1961 (Folder 14, Box 149)
  - Summer, 1938 - 1981 (Folder 15, Box 149)
  - Sun Lof [?], 1932 - 1933 (Folder 16, Box 149)
  - Sun Lof[?], 1934 (Folder 17, Box 149)
  - Sun, 1935 - 1938 (Folder 1, Box 150)
  - Sun, 1939 - 1942 (Folder 2, Box 150)
  - Sun, 1942 - 1944 (Folder 3, Box 150)
  - Sun, 1945 - 1979 (Folder 4, Box 150)
  - Sun - Anti Endorse, 1933 - 1936 (Folder 5, Box 150)
  - Sun/Uearwater Flap, 1935 (Folder 6, Box 150)
  - Sun Contract, 1945 (Folder 7, Box 150)
  - Sun - 36 Convention, 1936 (Folder 8, Box 150)
  - Sun Dealer's Meetings & Film, 1934 (Folder 9, Box 150)
  - Sun Emblems, 1934 - 1946 (Folder 10, Box 150)
  - Sun Film, 1976 (Folder 11, Box 150)
  - Sun - Line Charges, 1946 (Folder 12, Box 150)
  - Sun - LT [Lowell Thomas] Independent Contractor, 1938 (Folder 13, Box 150)
  - Sun - LT [Lowell Thomas] Image, 1934 (Folder 14, Box 150)
  - Sun - Press Service (" Fair "), 1942 (Folder 15, Box 150)
  - Sun - Set Up, 1933 (Folder 1, Box 151)
  - Sun Stock, 1933 - 1940 (Folder 2, Box 151)
  - Sun War, 1939 - 1941 (Folder 3, Box 151)
  - Sun & World Letters & Barton, undated (Folder 4, Box 151)
  - Sun Derland, Thomas E., 1965 (Folder 5, Box 151)
  - Swain, Robert, 1970 (Folder 6, Box 151)
  - Swenberg, Stanley, 1917 - 1979 (Folder 7, Box 151)
  - Swayze, John Cameron, 1956 (Folder 8, Box 151)
  - Sweet, Bob, 1963 (Folder 9, Box 151)
  - Symington, 1948 (Folder 10, Box 151)
  - Syracuse Debacle, 1947 (Folder 11, Box 151)
  - Tagore [1], undated (Folder 12, Box 151)
  - Tagore [2], undated (Folder 13, Box 151)
  - Tagore, 1970 (Folder 14, Box 151)
  - Tahiti Bomb, 1965 (Folder 15, Box 151)
  - Talks, 1931 - 1979 (Folder 16, Box 151)
  - Talks - Cancel, 1930 - 1931 (Folder 17, Box 151)
  - Talks - Cancel - Remote, 1930 (Folder 18, Box 151)
  - Talks Flap, 1956 (Folder 19, Box 151)
  - Talks - Hicks, 1946 (Folder 20, Box 151)